Guide to the International Center for Transitional Justice (ICTJ) records, 1918-2020, bulk 1970-2020 RL.01304
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Program and Subject Files, 1979-2015
  - ICTJ Programs, 1979-2014
    - Truth and Reconciliation Commissions: Audiovisual Materials
      - Liberia
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-03; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0547)
          #246 Rivercess Day 3, Sammy Darway
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-03; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0548)
          #247 Rivercess Day 3, Victoria Vigbay
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-03; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0549)
          #248 Rivercess Day 3, Martha Brown
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-03; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0550)
          #249 Rivercess Day 3, Makonni Gbotoe
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-03; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0551)
          #250 Rivercess Day 3, Jessay Wrotolo
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-03-11; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0552)
          #251 Sinoe Day 2, Brown B. Dorma
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-03-11; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0553)
          #252 Sinoe Day 2, Ester Saydee
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-03-11; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0554)
          #253 Sinoe Day 2, Roland Smith
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0515)
          #214 River Gee Day 2, Daniel T. Sackor
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0516)
          #215 River Gee Day 2, Wilson Saweayea
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0517)
          #216 River Gee Day 3, Jackson T. Slopor
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0518)
          #217 River Gee Day 3, Jackson T. Slopor (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0519)
          #218 River Gee Day 3, Mamie Slopor
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0520)
          #219 River Gee Day 3, Dickson W. Barley
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0521)
          #220 River Gee Day 3, Dickson W. Barley (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0522)
          #221 River Gee Day 3, Dickson W. Barley (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0523)
          #222 River Gee Day 3, Rose Beweh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0524)
          #223 River Gee Day 3, Joseph S. Quenah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0525)
          #224 River Gee Day 3, Elsay Collins
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0526)
          #225 River Gee Day 3, Theresa Choloplay
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0527)
          #226 River Gee Day 3, Zico N. Dardieh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-27; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0528)
          #227 River Gee Day 3, Brown Nyagbe
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-28; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0529)
          #228 River Gee Day 4, John T. Cooper Sr.
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-28; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0530)
          #229 River Gee Day 4, Tiseray Quaye-Chair
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-28; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0531)
          #230 River Gee Day 4, Mrs. Martha Watkins and Washington Moore Victim and alleged Perpetrator, respectively
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-29; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0532)
          #231 River Gee Day 5, Jackson C. Nyepan
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-29; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0533)
          #232 River Gee Day 5, Parl Saydee
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-29; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0534)
          #233 River Gee Day 5, Rev. Anthony N. Chea
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-30; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0495)
          #194 Montserrado Day 14, Dorethy Mulbah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-30; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0496)
          #195 Montserrado Day 14, Armstrong Nagbe
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-30; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0497)
          #196 Montserrado Day 14, Jeff Neeray
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-30; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0498)
          #197 Montserrado Day 14, Jeff Neeray
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-31; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0499)
          #198 Montserrado Day 15, Sam M. Kabah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-14; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0500)
          #199 Montserrado Day 4, Ugin Gray (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0501)
          #200 River Gee Day 1, Otis Daniel Ogunti
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0502)
          #201 River Gee Day 1, Solo B. Teah Sr.
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0503)
          #202 River Gee Day 1, Elizabeth Brownell
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0504)
          #203 River Gee Day 1, Oretha Cholo
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0505)
          #204 River Gee Day 1, Hilary Nyenaoh Watkins
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0506)
          #205 River Gee Day 1, Esther Tinneh Sokolo
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0507)
          #206 River Gee Day 1, Martha Watkins
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0508)
          #207 River Gee Day 1, Martha Watkins (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-25; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0509)
          #208 River Gee Day 1, Martha Teleh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0510)
          #209 River Gee Day 2, Anges Keh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0511)
          #210 River Gee Day 2, Emannuel Nyepan Sukuta
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0512)
          #211 River Gee Day 2, Roseline K. The
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0513)
          #212 River Gee Day 2, Michael Freeman
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-26; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0514)
          #213 River Gee Day 2, Isaac Sukuta Sukua
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-16; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0475)
          #174 Montserrado Day 6, Peter Yorksah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-16; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0476)
          #175 Montserrado Day 6, Lee Tommy Kiada
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-17; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0477)
          #176 Montserrado Day 7, Philip Zodou
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-17; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0478)
          #177 Montserrado Day 7, Gbasay Kamara
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0479)
          #178 Montserrado Day 8, Alfred Suah Debleh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0480)
          #179 Montserrado Day 8, Joe T.Y. Lesole
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0481)
          #180 Montserrado Day 8, Joe T.Y. Lesole
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0482)
          #181 Montserrado Day 8, Evelyn Juah Wessah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-22; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0483)
          #182 Montserrado Day 9, James Paul
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-22; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0484)
          #183 Montserrado Day 9, Samuel D. Karnley
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-23; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0485)
          #184 Montserrado Day 10, Tarnu Johnson
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-23; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0486)
          #185 Montserrado Day 10, Oretha Williams
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-23; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0487)
          #186 Montserrado Day 10, Solomon Gonleh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-23; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0488)
          #187 Montserrado Day 10, James Kerkula
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-23; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0489)
          #188 Montserrado Day 10, Prince Boika Perry
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-24; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0490)
          #189 Montserrado Day 11, Annie J. Smallwood
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-24; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0491)
          #190 Montserrado Day 11, Morris A. Padmore
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-24; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0492)
          #191 Montserrado Day 11, Joseph Kamara
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-28; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0493)
          #192 Montserrado Day 12, Krubo Eyeah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-29; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0494)
          #193 Montserrado Day 13, James Dudu Thomas
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0461)
          #160 Lofa Day 2, Morris Fayah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0462)
          #161 Lofa Day 2, Moses Kanneh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-16; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0463)
          #162 Lofa Day 3, John T. Kamara
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-16; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0464)
          #163 Lofa Day 3, Hannah Varney
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-16; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0465)
          #164 Lofa Day 3, George Kimba
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-08; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0466)
          #165 Montserrado Day 1, David D. Saweh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-08; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0467)
          #166 Montserrado Day 1, Dr. Jeremiah Walker
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-08; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0468)
          #167 Montserrado Day 1, James Meah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-10; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0469)
          #168 Montserrado Day 3, Gladice Arthur
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-14; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0470)
          #169 Montserrado Day 4, Ugin Gray
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-14; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0471)
          #170 Montserrado Day 4, Emmett Gray
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-14; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0472)
          #171 Montserrado Day 4, Boima Ballah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-14; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0473)
          #172 Montserrado Day 4, Mohammed D. Gray
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-01-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0474)
          #173 Montserrado Day 5, Joshua Milton Blayea
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0446)
          #145 Grand Kru Day 4, Children's Workshop
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0447)
          #146 Grand Kru Day 4, John Nyantee
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0448)
          #147 Grand Kru Day 4, Mrs. Anna J. Wreh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0449)
          #148 Grand Kru Day 4, Jacob Kortie Nyewon
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0450)
          #149 Grand Kru Day 4, Benedict S. Sayeh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0451)
          #150 Grand Kru Day 4, Winston Flomo
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-21; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0452)
          #151 Grand Kru Day 4, Isaac Tisuduail
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-22; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0453)
          #152 Grand Kru Day 5, Mariah Bayoh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-02-20; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0454)
          #153 Grand Kru Day 3, Augustine G. Nyanfor (duplicate)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0455)
          #154 Lofa Day 2, Brimah Vanday
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0456)
          #155 Lofa Day 2, Marth Sackie
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0457)
          #156 Lofa Day 2, Martue Sialia
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0458)
          #157 Lofa Day 2, Korpo Mbamba
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0459)
          #158 Lofa Day 2, Ansumana Kanneh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-04-15; Mini-DV (Box 141, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0460)
          #159 Lofa Day 2, Fatu Kanneh
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-08-11; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0357)
          #55 University of Liberia Professor, former Information Minister, and rebel leader Alhaji G. V. Kromah